ARPIT YADAV

UX/UI Designer

Phone: +91 7755832447 Address: New Delhi, India

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/arpit-

yadav-a6a8b8171/

Email: Kishanshanu2@gmail.com

I'm passionate about making user-friendly, interactive and delightful user experience. I am influenced by the elegance of minimalism in design and take cues from my surroundings. My passion lies in building empathy, prototyping concepts, and iterating for the solution.

EXPERIENCE

Lattice Innovations, Delhi

November 2022 - Present

UI/UX Designer

- Leveraged a deep understanding of system scope, workflows, and use cases to drive user-centric design.
- Translated complex requirements into clear and intuitive system design diagrams, including interaction and content maps.
- Utilized Figma to create mobile and web screens aligned with the design guide and Google's principles, ensuring seamless user experiences.
- Collaborated closely with developers and product managers to ensure designs were implemented accurately, resulting in a 30% reduction in post-launch bugs.
- Streamlined the prototyping process, reducing design iteration time by 20% and resulting in faster development cycles.
- Balanced design choices for efficiency, leading to practical and visually appealing solutions.

upUgo Fitness & Sports, India

April 2022 - November 2022

UI / UX designer

- Understanding brand identity and effectively applying style guides. Consistently maintained and enhanced the brand's visual consistency.
- Tackled visual design challenges by providing creative and versatile solutions.
- Thrived in an agile development environment, effectively communicating ideas to engineers and stakeholders.
- Continually tracked and analyzed key performance indicators (KPIs) to measure the success of design implementations.

EDUCATION

CGC College of Engineering, Landran

January 2018 - December 2022

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Electrical, Electronics and Communications Engineering

SKILLS

UI/UX, Information architecture, Wireframing, Prototyping, Collaboration, Figma, Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator

CERTIFICATIONS

Start the UX Design Process: Empathize, Define, and Ideate

March 2022

Coursera

Certificate link

Foundations of User Experience (UX) Design

February 2022

Coursera

Certificate link